>> Jem Young: 现在我们要谈的是这个奇怪的词
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Now we get to talk about
this weird word that I ran across
当我还是第一位工程师的时候
when I was first an engineer.
我就像个" nginx"
And I was like nginx?
N-ginx?
我帮你省得麻烦你读了很多
I'll save you the trouble cuz
you probably read a lot and
不知道它是怎么发音的是引擎
don't know how it's pronounced,
it's pronounced engine-x.
在软件应用程序的历史中诚实的是
Which honestly in the history of software
applications is the coolest name of
都是时候了
all time.
就像你在做什么
It's like, what do you work on?
恩金克斯
Nginx.
它是做什么的
What does it do?
一点都不知道
A little bit of everything.
人们都很喜欢
People are like whoa.
Nginx 是其中最受欢迎的网络服务器之一。
Nginx is one of the most
popular web servers out there.
这就是我们今天要做的
It's what we're gonna run today.
另一个你可能听说过的是阿帕奇，阿帕奇是另一个受欢迎的。
The other one you've probably heard of
is Apache, which is another popular one.
Apache 有点不同，配置了很多不同。
Apache is a little bit different and
it configures a lot different.
但如果我们使用 PHP，我肯定会使用 Apache ，因为 PHP 和
But if we're using PHP, I'd be
definitely using Apache, because PHP and
阿帕奇的手，他们的工作真的非常好。
Apache go hand in hand,
they work really, really well.
它们太好了其实就是 LAMP 堆。
They go so well it's actually
it's known as the LAMP stack.
有人知道 LAMP 的堆栈代表什么吗 ?
Anybody know what the LAMP
stack stands for?
>> 扬声器 2: Linux， Apache， Mongo- >> 扬声器 3: MySQL。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Linux, Apache, Mongo-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: MySQL.
>> 扬声器 2: MySQL 和 PHP。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: MySQL and PHP.
>> Jem Young: 没错
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yep, exactly.
但无论如何阿帕奇是你职业生涯中的另一个
But anyways, Apache is another one you
might run into in your careers as a full
或任何类型的工程师
stack engineer or any sort of engineer.
但今天我们要用牙龈
But today we're gonna use Nginx.
我爱的是它的轻量，速度极快。
I love Nginx cuz it's lightweight,
it is extremely fast.
我想思考的是多快能处理更多的请求
I'm trying to think how fast, it can
handle more requests than you can throw at
它比你的服务器还能处理好
it than your server can handle,
put it that way.
太快了
It's that fast.
它是一个逆向代理，它是一个 Web 服务器，它是一个代理服务器，它是一个文件服务器，
It's a reverse proxy, it's a web server,
it's a proxy server, it's a file server,
它可以进行高速缓存，可以进行性能调整。
it can do caching,
it can do performance tuning.
它可以压缩您的文件，将其发送出去，它可以处理您的加密。
It can compress your file, send it out,
it can handle your encryption.
Nginx 做了一点点的事情，真的是很棒的软件。
Nginx does a little bit of everything and
honestly it's amazing software.
但是我们今天不太深入
But, we're not gonna go
too deep into it today,
我们只能用它了
we're just gonna use it just enough.
因为我们可以非常深入地去压缩我们的 G - 拉链
Because we can go really, really deep
where we're compressing our G-zip
水平达到三级水平，我们正在调整我们的网络套接字。
levels to like level three, and
we're tuning our web sockets.
明天我们也许会这样做取决于我们今天的表现但今天
We might do that tomorrow, depending
on how well we do today, but for today,
我们会把这个配置好的
we're just gonna configure this.
所以我们想做的第一件事是
So the first thing we wanna do is,
实际上，我应该解释 Web 服务器的工作。
actually I should explain
what a web server does.
我们有一个服务器，我们只有一个基本的服务器，
We have a server,
we have just a basic server,
服务器本身什么都不做
the server itself doesn't do anything.
其实现在连请求都没有回应，
In fact it doesn't even
respond to requests right now,
因为它什么都没做
because it's not set up to do anything.
所以请点击您的服务器， >> Jem Young: What do?
So requests hit your server,
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: What do?
我们得想想办法
We have to figure out something,
我们得想想那个请求应该去哪里
we have to figure out where
that request should go.
是否应该转至应用程序?
Should it go to the app?
它应该去数据库吗
Should it go to the database?
是否要完全转至另一个服务器 ?
Should it go to a different
server entirely?
我不知道这就是 Nginx 在那儿的原因
I don't know, that's why Nginx is there.
Nginx 帮助将这些请求路由到正确的东西。
Nginx helps route those
requests to the right thing.
这就是为什么它有时被称为逆向代理
That's why it's called
a reverse proxy sometimes,
因为它需要一个请求，并在其他地方代理它。
because it takes one request and
it proxies it somewhere else.
Versus 是一个常规代理，需要执行一系列请求并将它们代理到一个位置。
Versus a regular proxy which takes a bunch
of requests and proxies them to one place.
大多数时候你会听到它叫逆向代理但是
You'll hear it called reverse
proxy most of the time, but
它真的是一个网络服务器，它做了很多事情。
it's really a web server,
it does a lot of things.
但 Nginx 是我们今天做的一件事的关键之一。
But Nginx is one the crux of one
of the things we're doing today.
我想说的比我们要建的实际应用更重要
I would say it's more important than
the actual application we're building is
正确调整 Nginx 。
tuning Nginx properly.
让我们安装 Nginx。
So let's install Nginx.
>> Jem Young: 因为我们不再是根了，我们一直都要用 sudo
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Because we're not root
anymore, we have to use sudo all the time
来安装新软件，因此很适合安装 nginx。
to install new software,
so sudo apt install nginx.
我现在就这么做了它可能要花一分钟的时间
And I'll just do that now
cuz it might take a minute.
>> Jem Young: 是。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yes.
>> Jem Young: 在安装随机位的同时，您不需要
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And while that's installing
random bits of trivia you don't need to
知道，有一个叫 " 是 " 的命令，它的所有类型都是 Y型的。
know, there's a command called yes,
which all it does is type y.
你就知道为什么会有这种事吗
And you're like why does that exist?
我们可以用这个人页面
We can use the man page.
它只输出你想要的东西通常是肯定的
It just outputs anything you want,
usually it's yes.
所以如果你想安装一堆软件
So if you wanted to install
a bunch of software and
你不想继续打字
you didn't want to keep typing yes.
你可以打个合适的装，管它，它会自动做的
You can hit apt install, pipe it to y,
it'll automatically do yes for
一切都结束了
everything until it exits.
你不需要知道的事情，但是你现在做了，你不可能不知道。
Little things you didn't need to know,
but you do now, you can't unknow it.
好了我们要启动 Nginx ，所以 sudo service nginx 启动。
All right, so then we're gonna start
Nginx, so sudo service nginx start.
Sudo 服务 nginx 启动。
Sudo service nginx start.
>> Jem Young: Anginx 已启动并正在运行 >> Jem Young: And
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And Nginx is up and running
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And
所以我们来测试这个让我们测试这个坏小子
so let's test this out,
let's test this bad boy out.
如果我的域设置未完成，请允许我复制我的 IP 。
Let me copy my IP just in case my
domain setup did not go through.
说的是最棒的
And say, jemisthebest,
好吧最好的点
whoop, jem I-S dot best.
好了好了
All right, it works.
这看起来很简单，但记住我们要经历的所有步骤
And this seems really simple, but remember
all the steps we had to go through to
配置我们的名称服务器，并获取我们的 DNS 记录。
configure our name servers,
and get our DNS records.
然后启动服务器并安装并使服务器启动并运行， SSH 和
Then start the server and install and get
our server up and running, the SSH, and
我们把它都跑了现在我们拿到了这个 Nginx 的网页
we got it all running, and
now we get this Nginx page.
就是这些小东西
It's the little things,
更重要的是你了解到这里的所有步骤
more importantly is you understand
all the steps it took to get here.
看起来真的很简单但你知道这不是
And it seems really, really simple,
but you know that it's not,
在车篷下面做了很多工作
underneath the hood was a lot of work.
太好了我应该和你分享这个剧本
Awesome, I should have shared
this screenshot with you,
当我买下我的版图时就花了我 1.80 美元
when I bought my domain it cost me $1.80.
看到 ICAN 的费用吗 ?
And see that ICAN fee?
记得我说过有一个司法机构控制所有东西
Remember I talked about there's this
registrar that controls all the stuff, so
我不知道这是什么，所以我只付出了 0.18 美元的费用。
I don't know what this is, and
so I just paid a $0.18 fee.
当你买一个域名的时候，你就会更新它，
Whenever you buy a domain, you renew it,
你总是付这么小的小费帮助保持互联网的运行
you're always paying this little tiny fee
that helps keep the Internet running.
所以如果你想知道那是什么，那就是原因。
So if you're ever wondering what that is,
that's why.
>> Jem Young: 太棒了，每个人都看到 Nginx 页面了吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Awesome,
is everybody seeing the Nginx page?
希望如果您不购买域，请仅输入 IP。
Hopefully, if you didn't buy a domain,
just type in your IP.
所以我也能做到这一点我也会得到同样的东西
So I can also do that and
I'm gonna get the same thing.
>> Jem Young: 如果我真的想获得战术，我就能在港口里
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And if I really want to
get tactical, I can type in the port
80 号是缺省端口我要再次得到同样的东西
80 which is the default port and
I'm gonna get the same thing again.
Nginx 现在在 80 号口运行
Nginx is now running on port 80,
它会自动打开防火墙给您 80 端口，我们不需要这样做。
it automatically opens the firewall to
port 80 for you, we don't have to do that.
明天我们要讨论防火墙并适当地配置防火墙
And tomorrow we're gonna talk about
firewalls and configuring them properly,
但今天不是
but not today.
>> Jem Young: 好的，每个人都跟我一起吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Okay, is everybody with me?
如果你不在这里
If you're not here,
我要说的一切都不会有任何意义
pretty much everything else I'm
gonna say will not make any sense.
好，现在，我们问了一个问题，网络是怎么工作的 ?
Cool, so now, we asked the causing
question, how does the Internet work?
有一个域，它命中一个名称服务器，名称服务器说，哎，
There's a domain, it hits a name server,
the name server says, hey,
我知道你想去哪儿
I know where you're trying to go.
这里是 IP， IP 被传递给其他路由器和节点和交换机，
Here's the IP, the IP gets passed off to
other routers and nodes and switches,
最终击中了你的服务器
eventually hits your server.
当它点击您的服务器时，它会说我现在做什么吗 ?
When it hits your server,
it says what I do now?
恩金克斯说我知道去哪我要把你转到这个默认页面上
Nginx says, hey, I know where to go,
I'm gonna route you to this default page,
只是一个空白的 HTML 页面。
just a blank HTML page.
现在很多互联网都是这样运作的
That's how a lot of the Internet works so
far, and
我们会慢慢积累起来直到它变得越来越复杂
we're gonna slowly build up until
it gets more and more complex.
在你成为主人之前，有人会说主子。
Until you'll be masters,
some say frontend masters.